(Leonard:)Oh, watch out, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)This little boy Casper
is a gh... Gh... Gh... Ghost!
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Droll.
Eh, not as droll as a grown man
passed out in a puddle of his own urine.
(Leonard:)That was pretty droll.
With a hint of ammonia.
(Sheldon:)Yes, enjoy your japes, gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)Think you've poked fun
at a milquetoast academic.
(Sheldon:)You've forgotten one thing.
(Sheldon:)I am also a son of the Lone Star State.
I'm Texas through and through.
(Sheldon:)And we know how
to settle scores down there.
(Sheldon:)If you doubt me, ask Mexico.
Hot girl, 9 o'clock.
(Stuart:)Don't everybody look at once.
(Raj:)What is she doing
in a comic book store?
(Stuart:)I don't know. She might be lost.
(Stuart:)Doesn't matter. Watch and learn.